[
    	{
		"Number": "1",
		"Fragment": "It is a beautiful summer day. The sun shines warmly on an old house near a river <audio src='https://manastoriesaudios.s3.amazonaws.com/1.stream+in+the+farm.mp3' /> behind the house a mother duck is sitting on six eggs <audio src='https://manastoriesaudios.s3.amazonaws.com/4.one+old+duck.mp3' />",
		"Question": "Is this old house close to: ",
		"Options": "a lake, or a river?",
		"Answer": "river",
		"AnswerOption": "2",
		"Explanation": "The old house is close to a river",
		"SecondQuestion":"Let's try again, is the old house close to a river? Answer saying: Yes, or No",
		"BinaryAnswer": "Yes"
    },
    {
		"Number": "2",
		"Fragment": "One by one, the eggs break open <audio src='https://manastoriesaudios.s3.amazonaws.com/3.1continual+egg+cracking.mp3' /> most of them break open except one, a big grey egg.",
		"Question": "What color is  the biggest egg? ",
		"Options": "is it grey, or white?",
		"Answer": "grey",
		"AnswerOption": "1",
		"Explanation": "The biggest egg is grey",
		"SecondQuestion":"Let's try again, is the biggest egg grey? Answer saying: Yes, or No",
		"BinaryAnswer": "Yes"
    },
    {
		"Number": "3",
		"Fragment": "Mother duck sits and sits on the big egg. At last it breaks open, out of it jumps the last baby duck <audio src='https://manastoriesaudios.s3.amazonaws.com/2.1+baby+duck.mp3' /> It looks big and strong, but grey and ugly.",
		"Question": "What color was the last baby duck?",
		"Options": "Was it grey, or yellow?",
		"Answer": "grey",
		"AnswerOption": "1",
		"Explanation": "The last baby duck was grey and ugly",
		"SecondQuestion":"Let's try again, do you think the last baby duck was grey? Answer saying: Yes, or No",
		"BinaryAnswer": "Yes"
    },
    {
		"Number": "4",
		"Fragment": "The next day mother duck takes all her little ducks to the river <audio src='https://manastoriesaudios.s3.amazonaws.com/2.2lots+of+ducks.mp3' /><audio src='https://manastoriesaudios.s3.amazonaws.com/4.one+old+duck.mp3' /> She jumps into the river <audio src='https://manastoriesaudios.s3.amazonaws.com/5.bigsplash.mp3' /> then all her baby ducks jump in too.",
		"Question": "Who jumped into the river?",
		"Options": "the ugly duckling, or all the baby ducks?",
		"Answer": "all the baby ducks",
		"AnswerOption": "2",
		"Explanation": "All of them including the big ugly duckling jumped into the river",
		"SecondQuestion":"Let's try again, did all the baby ducks jumped into the river? Answer saying: Yes, or No",
		"BinaryAnswer": "Yes"
    },
    {
		"Number": "5",
		"Fragment": " <voice name='Ivy'> Come with me to the farm yard ! </voice> says mother duck to her baby ducks, and they all follow her there. The farm yard is a noisy place <audio src='https://manastoriesaudios.s3.amazonaws.com/0.farm.mp3' /> The poor duckling is so unhappy there. The rooster flies at him <audio src='https://manastoriesaudios.s3.amazonaws.com/8.rooster+flying.mp3' /> and the farmer kicks him <audio src='https://manastoriesaudios.s3.amazonaws.com/9.get-out-of-my-house-female-angry-yelling.mp3' />",
		"Question": "How does the ugly duckling feel?",
		"Options": "Is it happy, or sad?",
		"Answer": "sad",
		"AnswerOption": "2",
		"Explanation": "The ugly ducking feels sad",
		"SecondQuestion":"Let's try again, do you think the last baby duck feels sad? Answer saying: Yes, or No",
		"BinaryAnswer": "Yes"
    },
    {
		"Number": "6",
		"Fragment": "At last one day he runs away. He comes to a river <audio src='https://manastoriesaudios.s3.amazonaws.com/1.stream+in+the+farm.mp3' /> He sees many beautiful big birds swimming there. Their feathers are so white, their necks so long, and their wings so pretty <audio src='https://manastoriesaudios.s3.amazonaws.com/10.swansflyby.mp3' /> The little duckling looks and looks at them, he wants to stay and watch them. He wants to be beautiful like them.",
		"Question": "What animals do you think they are?",
		"Options": "Are they ducks, or swans?",
		"Answer": "swans",
		"AnswerOption": "2",
		"Explanation": "Swans are typically bigger and whiter than ducks",
		"SecondQuestion":"Let's try again, do you think the animals are swans? Answer saying: Yes, or No",
		"BinaryAnswer": "Yes"
    }
]